PALUDGNACH MATTEO

Full-Stack Software developer

SKILLS

FRONTEND

sveltekit - tailwind - flutter

BACKEND

typescript - golang

DEVOPS

github actions - argocd - kubernetes

DATABASES

postgres - redis - mongodb

CONTACTS

- **1** +39 3518853376
- ☑ paludgnachmatteo.dev@gmail.com
- portfolio.mp281x.xyz
- Moimacco (UD)

LANGUAGES

ITALIAN - native

ENGLISH - B2

SUMMARY

For several years I have been deeply passionate about web, application and API development by utilizing technologies such as Typescript, SvelteKit, Flutter, Golang, Postgres, Redis and MongoDB.

Additionally I have an interest in DevOps, employing technologies like Docker and Kubernetes, UI/UX design and project planning.

I am punctual and reliable due to my initiative and organizational skills, and I endeavor to consistently bring fresh ideas to the table.

WORK EXPERIENCE

BIZAWAY (stage) 12/06/2023 - 04/08/2023 Backend Developer Spilimbergo (IT)

NORDEST SERVIZI (stage) 17/01/2022 - 29/01/2022 System Engineer Tavagnacco (IT)

EDUCATION

ITS Alto Adriatico 2022 - 2024 Final vote: -- EQF: 5

Tecnico Superiore Cloud Developer

ISIS A. Malignani 2017 - 2022

Final vote: 68 EQF: 4

IT and Telecomunications Diploma

I authorize the processing of my personal data contained in my CV in accordance with Article 13 of Legislative Decree No. 196 of June 30, 2003 - "Code regarding the protection of personal data" and Article 13 of GDPR 679/16 - "European Regulation on the protection of personal data."